SUBHATRA CHETTIAR

Address Dombivli , Maharashtra, 421202.

Email Address

chettiarsubhatra@gmail.com

Contact details 9324224423

DOB-16/06/1989

Summary

Junior accountant with a 3 year experience accountant who possessess the ability to analyze data, define problem areas, draw logical conclusions, analyze situations accurately and adopt an effective course of action. Who is accustomed to the pressure to tight deadlines and possesses the ability to excel in a fast-paced environment. Manifest capacity to manage numerous projects concurrently. Able company spokesperson who always presents an image that will promote the company.

Objective

- Career growth in the area of banking, finance and accounting .
- 2. Quest to work and learn in a real professional and vying ambience that enables me to cope with the emerging as well as latest technology and scope for the widening the spectrum of my knowledge.

Core competency

- 1. Have intermediate level knowledge of Microsoft office package tools i.e. Word, Excel, PowerPoint etc.
- 2. An expertise in tally
- 3. Have a flair knowledge about Communication skills and managing the mob.

Professional Experiences

Organization PERICING SYSTEM INDIA PVT LTD

Designation Sales Co-Ordinator

and Back Office Support

Office support

Duration June 2013-April 2016

Roles and responsibilities

Co-Ordination with Business team and Vendors to solve the queries, Preparation of Voucher, Preparation of Bills.

Confirming Orders & coordinating with Representatives.

Reporting to Managing Director, Reporting Cost Centers\ Sales data to Managing Director, Handling petty Cash.

Organization GLOWFAB

INDUSTRIES PVT

Designation Junior Accountant **Duration** May 2010- May 2013

Roles and Responsibilities

Performed the processing duties of accounts payable including liaison with vendors staff to ensure prompt payment of invoice. Analyzed, audited and researched hundreds of invoices each month while directing the administration of all invoices. Verified completeness and accuracy of data and documentation for invoice data entry in order to facilitate month-end closings. With an understanding of accounting principles and concepts, assisted in month end closing procedures and reconciled the month end accounts payable trial balances and bank statements. Utilized excel, prepare a monthly list of all payable

transactions to submit to the owner for review.

Organization Wisdom Book

Distributor

Desgination junior accountant

Duration 2009-2010

Roles and responsibilities

Monitoring Account Related All Queries Co-Ordination with Business team and Vendors to solve the queries ,Handling Financial transaction, Preparation of Voucher , Bank Reconciliation, Handling petty Cash

Education

Course/ Examination	Institution/ university	year	performance
M.com in accountancy	Mumbai University	2010- 2012	A grade
B.com in accountancy	Mumbai University	2007- 2010	A grade
HSC	Maharashtra Board	2006- 2007	Distinction

Skills

Auditing, Inventory Management, Tax preparation, Cash Handling, calculate figures and amounts such as discounts, interest, commissions, proportions and percentages.